ILGWU International Relations Department publications 5780/062 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 6, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Turk-Is News Bulletin, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Confederation of Turkish Trade Unions. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 2 Lideres Para Una Situacion de Excepcion, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Fetracalp. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: 30 Years, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By CLAT News. Special Edition 30th Anniversary. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Acto Inaugural INAESIN, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Juan Jose Delpino y Antonio Rios. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Discurso Pronunciado por Juan Jose Delpino, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Estatutos Del Instituto de Altos Estudios Sindicales, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Instituto de Altos Estudios Sindicales. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Federacion de Trabajadores del cazado pieles cutiembres, anexos y similares de VZLA, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Inaesin Cuadernos, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Cuadernos del Inae. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 8: Que esPor quePara que, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Unidad y Conciliacion, Publication (Box 6, Folder 4)
    By Asamblea Nacional. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 6, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: El Intercambio Comercial en el Continente Americano; Analisis y Reaccion de los Sindicatos, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
    By AFL-CIO & American Institute for Free Labor Development. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: El Movimiento Laboral Latinoamericano y Ajustes Estructurales en la Decada de Los Noventa, Publication (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Box: 6, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions in Asia: Research, Publication (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Box: 6, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Struggle for Democracy in Central America, Publication (Box 6, Folder 7)
    By American Institute for Free Labor Development; Georgetown University International Labor Program; Social Democrats USA; The Labor Desk of the United States Youth Council. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Deomcratic Revolution, Publication (Box 6, Folder 8)
    By National Endowment for Democracy. Proceedings of a conference sponsored by the National Endowment for Democracy. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Eastern Europe Central Europe Europe, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By American Academy of Arts and Sciences. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newsnotes, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By Institute on East Central Europe - Columbia University. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Peace & Democracy News, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By Campaign for Peace and Democracy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Report on the Visit to Eastern Europe of the Senate Delegation Led by Senator John Heinz; Political and Economic Developments in Central and Eastern Europe and Their Implications for United States Foreign Economic Policy, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By U.S. Government Senate. 101st Congress 2nd Session. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Common Position on the Uruguay Round of the Largest European Manufacturers and the European Unions Textile and Clothing; for a Dynamic and Exporting European Industry, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Comite Syndical Europeen du Textile, De l'Habillement et du Cuir. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: CSCE Vienna Follow-Up Meeting; A Framework for Europe's Future, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By U.S. Department of State; Bureau of Public Affairs. Selected Documents No. 35, January 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: EUR 12: diagrams of the enlarged community; European File, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Europe and the New Technologies; Conference Report, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Economic and Social Committee of the European Communities. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Textiles and Clothing: A European Strategy; a TUC Strategy; A Statement by the TUC's Textile, Clothing and footwear Industries Committee on an EC Industrial Policy for Textiles and Clothing, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    By Trades Union Congress. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Europe Information; External Relations, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Europe Information; External Relations, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Europe Information; External Relations, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: The Trade Union Movement in the European Community; Trade Union Movement in Germany, Publication (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Box: 6, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Hemispheric Trade and the Workers, Publication (Box 6, Folder 12)
    By American Institute for Free Labor Development. AFL-CIO/AIFLD Third Annual Trade Union Western Hemisphere Economic Conference; Los Angeles, California. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Latin American Trade Unions and Employment Policies, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The Informal Dector and the Trade Union Movement in Latin America and the Caribbean; An Analysis and Proposals for Action, Publication (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Box: 6, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Conferencia Internacional Retos y Desafios del Sindcalismo Para El Ano, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    By Proyecto. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Critical Issues; Latin America; Crisis and Removal, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    By Miguel de la Madrid Hurtado. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Fititvc Voz, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    By Fititvc Voz. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Nuevos Rummbos, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    By Luis A. Anderson. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Sin Fronteras; Fraternales felicitaciones a todos los Delgados de la Cumbre Andina; Unidos en Fraterno Lazo de Amistad y de Cooperacion Hacia el Progreso de la Region Andina, Publication (Box 6, Folder 14)
    By Sudamtex. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 6, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Middle East and the Trilateral Countries, Publication (Box 6, Folder 15)
    By Garret FitzGerald; Hideo Kitahara; Arrigo Levi; Joseph J. Sisco. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: New Priorities in the Americas: Making Democracy Work, Publication (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Box: 6, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for applications for financial support from Nordic Unions to the trade union movement in developing countries, Publication (Box 6, Folder 17)
    By LO/FTF Council; TUSC; LO; LO/TCO. TWO COPIES. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The National Bipartisan Commission on Central America, Publication (Box 6, Folder 18)
    By Executive Director William C. Doherty Jr. Item is in English.
- Box: 6, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Libson 1992, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    By The Trilateral Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Patterns of Change: Report of the Textile, Clothing and Footwear Industries Tripartite Overseas Mission, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    By The Department of Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Workers Rights and the New World Order, Publication (Box 6, Folder 19)
    By Charles Karnaghan; Barbara Briggs. TWO COPIES. Item is in English.
- Box: 7, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Informe Annual Sobre Las Violaciones De Los Derechos Sindicales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Confederacion International De Organizaciones Sindicales Libres. Item is in French.
  - Item 2: Rapport Annuel Sur Les Violations Des Droits Syndicaux, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Confederation Internationale Des Syndicats Libres. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 7, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Informe Annual Sobre Las Violaciones De Los Derechos Sindicales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Confederacion Internacional De Organizaciones Sindicales Libres. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Rapport Annuel Sur Les Violations Des Droits Syndicaux, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Confederation Internationale Des Syndicates Libres. Item is in French.
- Box: 7, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Informe Annual Sobre Las Violaciones De Los Derechos Sindicales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Rapport Annuel Sur Les Violations Des Droits Syndicaux, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Confederation Internationale Des Syndicats Libres. Item is in French.
  - Item 3: Trade Union Rights: Survey of Violations, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 7, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual Survey on Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Annual Survey on Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Informe Annual Sobre Las Violaciones De Los Derechos Sindicales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Rapport Annuel Sur Les violations Des Droits Syndicaux, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Examen Annual De Las Violaciones De Los Derechos Sindicales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By Confederacion Internacional de Organizaciones Sindicales Libres. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 7, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Annual Surveys of Violations of Trade Union Rights, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Examen Annual De Las Violaciones De Los Derechos Sindicales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Box: 8, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: On Organising Workers in the Informal Sector: A Report Prepared for the International Confederation of Free Unions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
    By Dr. Swasti Mitter. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 8, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and the Transnationals, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Issue 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: trade unions and the Transnationals, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Issue 2; 2 Copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 8, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1984 World Economic Review: The Reality of Interdependence, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. 1 copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1985 World Economic Review: Employment Development; A working document for the 4th World Women's Conference of the ICTU Madrid 23-26 April 1985, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. 3 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 8, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Breaking Down the Wall of Silence; How to Combat Child Labor, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Romper El Muro Del Silencio: Como Combatir el Trabajo Infantil, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 8, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Decisions of the 14th World Congress of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Melbourne, 14-18 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Challenge of Change: report to the 14th ICFTU World Congress on the Tasks Ahead for the International Confederation of Free Trade Union Movement, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. 14-18 March 1988, melbourne, Australia. Item is in English.
- Box: 8, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of the International Confederation of Free Trade Union Seminar on Positive Action, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 8, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ICFTU, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By ICFTU. No. 8/87, Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ICFTU AproLabor News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By ICFTU. Newspaper. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: ICFTU APROLabor News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By ICFTU. ICFTU May Day Manifesto 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: ICFTU APROLabour News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: ICFTU-ORIT Inter-American Labor News, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    By Publication of the Inter-American Regional Organization of Workers. Newspaper. Item is in English.
- Box: 8, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: FLWWOMEN: Supplement to the Journal of the International Confederatin of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. March 1995, N 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Priorities and Criteria for Project Selection, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Supplement Inter-American Labor News: World Summit in Pro of Infance, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. N. 2, September/December 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Working Women: ICFTU policies and programmes, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Box: 8, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Typology of Functions in Adult Education: a comparative study France-Spain-Sweden, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Box: 8, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Priorities and Criteria for Project Selection, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Trade Unions and the Transnationals: Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    By International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. Special Issue M 3 Export processing Zones. Item is in English.
- Box: 9, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ILO Principles, Standards And Procedures Concerning Freedom Of Association, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    By International Labor Office Geneva. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ILO Publications On Multinationals, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Women At Work, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Box: 9, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Workers Participation In Decisions Within Understangs, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Box: 9, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Working For Development, The Technical Cooperation Programme of the ILO, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    By ILO. Item is in English.
- Box: 9, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 75 Years of Making A Difference In The World Of Work, A Booklet Of Facts For Americans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    By ILO's Washington Branch Office. Item is in English.
- Box: 9, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Making A Difference In The World Of Work, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Box: 9, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Note on the Proceedings, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    By International Labour Organization. Item is in English.
- Box: 9, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Third Technical Tripartite Meeting For The Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Box: 9, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Textiles Committee, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    By International Labour Organisation. Item is in English.
- Box: 9, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Second Tripartite Technical Meeting For The Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Box: 9, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Textiles Committee, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Box: 9, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: World Employment 1995, Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Box: 9, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The International Labor Organization, Facts For Americans, Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Box: 9, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Third Tripartite Technical Meeting For The Clothing Industry, The Impact On Employment And Income Of Structural And Technological Change In The Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Box: 10, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the Director-General, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    International Labour Conference, 69th Session, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of the Director-General: Appendices, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    International Labour conference, 69th session, 1983. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The World Employment Programme: What it is, what it does, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Box: 10, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The practice of entrepreneurship, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    By Geoffrey G. Meredith; Robert E. Nelson; Philip A. Neck. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minimum wage fixing, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    By Gerald Starr. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Legislative Series 1183: A selection of world labour and social security legislation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Box: 10, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Recent Developments in the Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    By Sectoral Activities Programme. Fourth Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry, Report I. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Recent developments in the clothing industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The effects of technological changes in the clothing industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    By Sectoral Activities Programme. Fourth Tripartite Technical Meeting for the Clothing Industry, Report II. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The effects of technological changes in the clothing industry, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Tripartite approaches to labour dispute settlement in the Asean region, the Republic of Korea & Japan Bangkok, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    By Michael Baumann. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Summaries of International Labour Standards, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Box: 10, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The United States and the International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    By Louis B. Sohn; Daniel G. Partan; Paul C. Irwin. Twenty- Sixth Report of the Commission to Study the Organization of Peace. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Children at Work, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
    By Elias Mendelievich. Item is in English.
- Box: 10, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Conditions of Work in the Textile Industry, including Problems related to Organisation of work, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    By Programme of Industrial Activities. Textiles Committee, Tenth Session, Report III. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Training Requirements in the Textile Industry in the Light of Changes in the Occupational Structure, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    By Programme of Industrial Activities. Textiles Committee, Tenth Session, Report II. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Meeting of Experts on the Social Protection of Homeworkers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    By International Labour Office. Technical background document. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: International Labour Review 1983, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    By International Labour Office. Vol. 122 No.5. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Social and Labour Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    By International Labour Office. Quarterly Publication No. 4, December 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Social and Labour Bulletin, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    By International Labour Office. Quarterly Publication No.3, September 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labour Education, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    By International Labour Office. No. 48. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Workers' Education and its Techniques: A Worker's Educational Manual, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    By International Labour Office. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Tripartite Declaration of Pinciples concerning Multinational Enterprises and Social Policy, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Tripartite Declaration of Principles concerning Multinational Enterprises and Social Policy, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    By International Labour Office. Second Edition. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Estatutos de la Federacion Internacional de Trabajadores de las Industrias Textiles, Vestido Y Cuero, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By International textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Full Employment and Growth as the Social and Economic Goal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. A Joint Statement by Biac and Tuac. Item is in French.
  - Item 3: Rules of the International textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By International textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Rules of the International textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Rules of the International textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: What it is & What it does, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Women's Health and Safety: Hazards in the Textile Garment and Leather Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    By Women's Health and Safety: Hazards in the textile garment and leather industry. Item is in English.
- Box: 11, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: ITGLWF Seminar on Asian FTZ's: Part II Country Reports, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ITGLWF Seminar on Asian FTZ's: Part II Country Reports, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    By International Textile, Garment & Leather Workers' Federation. 2nd copy. Item is in English.